

# RODRÍGUEZ SIRET **FRANK**Full Stack Developer

O Av. Federico Rey #4 Santiago de Cuba

**(**+53) 551 218 66

# SOCIAL

in @frank-siret

@FrankSiret

@FrankSiret

# **PROFILE**

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science & Full Stack Developer. With good skills in mathematics, algorithms, and programming languages. I have several years of experience and achievements in the labor field. I like to improve my skills and I always push myself the most.

# **EDUCATION**

## COMPUTER SCIECE

Universidad de Oriente - Cuba 2014 - 2019

- Graduated with Gold Title and Scientific Merit Award.
- One of the top students from the 2019 class.
- Several scientific events related to Computer Science.
- Participated for 5 years in the ICPC Competitive Programming achieving success in the Caribbean Finals.
- Degree Thesis in the field of Information Retrieval.

### SKILLS

- ReactJavaScript
- Html / Css
  TypeScript
- Sass C/C++
- Spring BootJava

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Full Stack Developer

From 2021 | PeopleWalking

- Designed and developed UI/UX application.
- Developed API Backend application using Spring Boot framework.
- Automate software development, such as build, test, and deployment, following CI/CD guidelines using Jenkins.
- Support junior developer boot camps on React JS and helped improve their knowledge in the library.
- Developed reusable components following React's concepts.
- Daily work progress reports following the workflow set by the team using Beanstalk source version control software and Jira software development Tool.

Technologies used

React JS Typescript Bootstrap 4 Ant Design Spring Boot PostgreSQL

## Computer Science Professor

From 2019 to 2022 | Universidad de Oriente

- **Teaches** classes of Logic Math and Data Structures and Algorithms.
- Won the annual CITMA Award for Young Researchers in 2019.

## Freelance Full Stack Developer

From 2020 to 2021 | Freelance

- Designed and developed websites for small business.
- Guided digital marketing strategy for positioning the business on the web.
- Worked in a team of two members using agile methodologies XP.

Technologies used

React JS Bootstrap 4 API Platform Swagger MYSQL

# C++ Developer

From 2017 to 2021 | Centro de Biofísica Médica

- Contributed to the design and development of the medical imaging software Imagis.
- Support junior developer on C++ and helped improve their knowledge in the language.
- Worked in more than 10 features such as design, report management, transmission, visualization, and image segmentation.

Technologies used

C++ Java VTK ITK DCMTK Qt Framework Lucene Information Retrieval

## CERTIFICATES

Problem Solving Certificate

React Certificate

Nov 2020 | HackerRank

Dec 2020 | HackerRank

JavaScript Certificate

Apr 2022 | HackerRank

## LANGUAGES

SpanishEnglish

# INTERESTS

